[
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Past tense of MAKE",
      "answers": ["makes", "maked", "made"],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Past tense of BUY",
      "answers": ["buyed", "bought", "buys"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Past tense of WATCH",
      "answers": ["watched", "watches", "watch"],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Past tense of BEGIN",
      "answers": ["began", "begun", "begined"],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Past tense of CHOOSE",
      "answers": ["choosed", "chosen", "chose"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Past tense of SPEAK",
      "answers": ["spoke", "spoken", "speaked"],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Past tense of STEAL",
      "answers": ["stealed", "stole", "stolen"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Past tense of CATCH",
      "answers": ["caught", "catched", "catches"],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Past tense of GO",
      "answers": ["gone", "goed", "went"],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Past tense of LEAVE",
      "answers": ["leaved", "leaves", "left"],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "Past tense of MEET",
      "answers": ["met", "meet", "meted"],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "Past tense of RECEIVE",
      "answers": ["receives", "received", "receiving"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "Past tense of DRINK",
      "answers": ["drank", "drunk", "drinking"],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "Past tense of KNOW",
      "answers": ["knew", "knowed", "known"],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "Past tense of FALL",
      "answers": ["falled", "fallen", "fell"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "Past tense of PROVE",
      "answers": ["proved", "proven", "proves"],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question": "Past tense of HEAR",
      "answers": ["hears", "heared", "heard"],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "question": "Past tense of DO",
      "answers": ["does", "did", "done"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "question": "Past tense of TEACH",
      "answers": ["teached", "taught", "teaches"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "question": "Past tense of BECOME",
      "answers": ["become", "became", "becomed"],
      "correct": 1
    }
  ]
  